

Okky Muhamad Budiman

Contact

Address

Bandung

Phone

085797178071

Email

budimanokky93@gmail.com

Skills

- PHP (Laravel, Yii, CI)
- NodeJS (ExpressJS)
- Golang (Gin-gonic)
- Java
- Html
- CSS
- JQuery
- ReactJS
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- AWS Lambda
- API
- RPC
- Websocket
- Docker

Professional Summary

Experienced in Software Development. Building system with many technologies and programming languages. Focusing on Web Development and Mobile Development. My Goals is to delivering products with good development cycles that will help smooth business process

Work Experience

03/2015 03/2016

Ciheul.com - Jr. Software Engineer (Bandung)

- Create website Front-end and Backend(PHP, NodeJS, AngularJS)
- Design Database Scheme(MySQL, PostgreSQL)

03/2016 - 04/2017

PT. Smooets Teknologi Outsourcing - Software Engineer (Bandung)

- Design and Implement DB Scheme
- Building Website(PHP, AngularJS, NodeJS) Delivering and maintenance Website
- Deployment project to production

09/2017 - 12/2018

GoUP Pte. Ltd - Software Engineer (Singapore)

- Design and Implement DB Scheme for GoUP Products
- Building Website Backend and Frontend(PHP, Go, NodeJS, VueJS, ReactJS)
- Delivering features and maintenance Products
- Deployment project to production

12/2018 - 08/2019

99.co - Software Engineer (Bandung)

- Design and Implement DB Scheme for 99.co Products
- Building Website Backend and Frontend(PHP, Go, VueJS)
- Delivering features and maintenance Products
- Deployment project to production

08/2019 - Now

Ralali.com - Software Engineer (Bandung)

- Building API for BigAgent Apps (Go)
- Delivering features and maintenance Products

Education

08/2011 - 08/2014

UNPAD - Information Technology

Diploma Degree

08/2015 - Now

WIDYATAMA UNIVERSITY - Informatics Engineer

Bachelor Degree

Languages

Indonesia

— C2 - Proficient

English — B2 - Upper-Intermediate

Sunda — C2 - Proficient